

Profile

Highly motivated and academically accomplished student with a strong commitment to learning and contributing to the advancement of knowledge in the field. Distinctive skills are: diligence, perseverance, curiosity, sociability. I have experience working with the following technology stack: C/C++, Python, Java, Qt, Android development.

Employment Experience

Resident of the Neimark IT-academy at "НЕЙМАРК", Nizhniy Novgorod

2022 — Present

Work with talented young people in Russia, helping to solve cases of leading companies in practice, which allows students to gain valuable experience in the IT industry. Over the course of several days, participants solve cases such as: olympiad programming, application development. One of my team won in the last category, having implemented with my support an application for analyzing the amount of lactate in the blood with a graph of the dependence of lactic acid salts in the blood on the time of exercise: click.

Private tutor for the Unified State Exam, Nizhniy Novgorod

2022 — Present

Prepare high school students (grades 10-11) for the Unified State Exam in specialized mathematics and computer science. Prepared more than 18 students. Topics covered were: interpolation, systems of nonlinear equations, convex polygons and their intersection areas, algorithms.

Education

Technical Lyceum #38, Nizhniy Novgorod

2019 - 2022

HSE University, Nizhniy Novgorod

2022 — Present

Applied Mathematics and Information Science

Courses

Samsung IT-School, Mobile development

2019 - 2020

Details

Nizhniy Novgorod Russian Federation +79308106722 pddMas@mail.ru

Date of birth 10.11.2003

Links

GitHub Telegram VK

Skills

Communication

Creativity

Adaptability

Fast Learner

Time Management

Teamwork

Languages

Russian

English

Hobbies

- Application development
- Tutoring (maths and informatics, Unified State Exam)
- Mathematics
- Squash and judo